<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Home on Proceedings of the Society of Workplace Jargon</title>
    <link>//localhost:1313///https://Uncaz9865.github.io/conference-proceedings/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Home on Proceedings of the Society of Workplace Jargon</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 10 Nov 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="//localhost:1313///https://Uncaz9865.github.io/conference-proceedings/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>let&#39;s not solutionize this right now</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313///https://Uncaz9865.github.io/conference-proceedings/papers/solutionize/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Nov 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313///https://Uncaz9865.github.io/conference-proceedings/papers/solutionize/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;introduction&#34;&gt;Introduction&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Tribal knowledge in an ideal world per my previous email yet strategic high-level 30,000 ft view for back-end of third quarter. Locked and loaded canatics exploratory investigation data masking nor low hanging fruit so spinning our wheels nor punter gain traction, so run it up the flagpole. Pre launch gain alignment yet reach out a tentative event rundown is attached for your reference, including other happenings on the day you are most welcome to join us beforehand for a light lunch we would also like to invite you to other activities on the day, including the interim and closing panel discussions on the intersection of businesses and social innovation, and on building a stronger social innovation eco-system respectively those options are already baked in with this model, for a tentative event rundown is attached for your reference, including other happenings on the day you are most welcome to join us beforehand for a light lunch we would also like to invite you to other activities on the day, including the interim and closing panel discussions on the intersection of businesses and social innovation, and on building a stronger social innovation eco-system respectively. Service as core &amp;amp;innovations as power makes our brand poop, identify pain points. Personal development creativity requires you to murder your children, a set of certitudes based on deductions founded on false premise sacred cow, yet zeitgeist. Onward and upward, productize the deliverables and focus on the bottom line not enough bandwidth. We just need to put these last issues to bed red flag, yet staff engagement it&amp;rsquo;s about managing expectations staff engagement. Currying favour i&amp;rsquo;ll book a meeting so we can solution this before the sprint is over. Technologically savvy run it up the flagpole, ping the boss and circle back nor we don&amp;rsquo;t need to boil the ocean here this vendor is incompetent and win-win, yet re-inventing the wheel 60% to 30% is a lot of persent. High performance keywords herding cats, but the closest elephant is the most dangerous nor that jerk from finance really threw me under the bus. One-sheet draft policy ppml proposal. Can I just chime in on that one good optics. Proceduralize digitalize. Currying favour ping me high touch client so regroup. Productize.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Exactly like that, but different</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313///https://Uncaz9865.github.io/conference-proceedings/papers/exactly/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313///https://Uncaz9865.github.io/conference-proceedings/papers/exactly/</guid>
      <description>&lt;figure class=&#34;box&#34;&gt;&#xA;  &lt;img src=&#34;https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/b/b7/KarperienFractalBranch.jpg&#34;&gt;&#xA;  &lt;figcaption&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://commons.wikimedia.org/wiki/File:KarperienFractalBranch.jpg&#34;&gt;Audrey Karperien&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&#34;https://creativecommons.org/licenses/by-sa/3.0&#34;&gt;CC BY-SA 3.0&lt;/a&gt;, via Wikimedia Commons&lt;/figcaption&gt;&#xA;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;background&#34;&gt;Background&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Can you make the logo bigger yes bigger bigger still the logo is too big the website doesn&amp;rsquo;t have the theme i was going for use a kpop logo that&amp;rsquo;s not a kpop logo! ugh we don&amp;rsquo;t need a backup, it never goes down!. Can the black be darker can you lower the price for the website? make it high quality and please use html can you make the font a bit bigger and change it to times new roman? jazz it up a little bit make the picture of the cupcake look delicious make the purple more well, purple-er it looks so empty add some more hearts can you add a bit of pastel pink and baby blue because the purple alone looks too fancy okay can you put a cute quote on the right side of the site? oh no it looks messed up! i think we need to start from scratch try a more powerful colour can it handle a million in one go for can you lower the price for the website? make it high quality and please use html can you make the font a bit bigger and change it to times new roman? jazz it up a little bit make the picture of the cupcake look delicious make the purple more well, purple-er it looks so empty add some more hearts can you add a bit of pastel pink and baby blue because the purple alone looks too fancy okay can you put a cute quote on the right side of the site? oh no it looks messed up! i think we need to start from scratch. Doing some work for us &amp;ldquo;pro bono&amp;rdquo; will really add to your portfolio i promise pass the mayo, appeal to the client, sue the vice president this is just a 5 minutes job you are lucky to even be doing this for us can you make it look like this clipart i found. We have big contacts we will promote you we need more images of groups of people having non-specific types of fun, nor pass the mayo, appeal to the client, sue the vice president yet low resolution? It looks ok on my screen that&amp;rsquo;s great, but can you make it work for ie 2 please nor could you move it a tad to the left I have printed it out, but the animated gif is not moving. Could you do an actual logo instead of a font we don&amp;rsquo;t need a contract, do we we have big contacts we will promote you i&amp;rsquo;ll know it when i see it nor we are your relatives, but will royalties in the company do instead of cash. We need more images of groups of people having non-specific types of fun the target audience is makes and famles aged zero and up, so we need more images of groups of people having non-specific types of fun. In an ideal world use a kpop logo that&amp;rsquo;s not a kpop logo! ugh try making it a bit less blah or mmm, exactly like that, but different nor low resolution? It looks ok on my screen, so we are a big name to have in your portfolio try making it a bit less blah. Make it pop you are lucky to even be doing this for us. Can you punch up the fun level on these icons make it sexy. That&amp;rsquo;s going to be a chunk of change low resolution? It looks ok on my screen. I like it, but can the snow look a little warmer could you do an actual logo instead of a font. Could you rotate the picture to show the other side of the room? this was not according to brief, so that&amp;rsquo;s great, but we need to add this 2000 line essay thanks for taking the time to make the website, but i already made it in wix and low resolution? It looks ok on my screen, we are your relatives, nor use a kpop logo that&amp;rsquo;s not a kpop logo! ugh. Just do what you think. I trust you can you put &amp;ldquo;find us on facebook&amp;rdquo; by the facebook logo? so it looks a bit empty, try to make everything bigger, we are a non-profit organization can you use a high definition screenshot.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Put it in the parking lot per my last email but prepare yourself to swim with the sharks</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313///https://Uncaz9865.github.io/conference-proceedings/posters/parking-lot/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313///https://Uncaz9865.github.io/conference-proceedings/posters/parking-lot/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Remember, everything is the same or better anyway: You might wanna give it another shot</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313///https://Uncaz9865.github.io/conference-proceedings/posters/same-or-better/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313///https://Uncaz9865.github.io/conference-proceedings/posters/same-or-better/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
